Let's introduce a model that has a split, asymmetrical shoulder, and a foldable shoulder.
In the shape, we can see that the original A-throat, first of all, it is an asymmetrical style, the original A-throat is gone, which means it has been transferred to the shoulder split line.
The original Xiu Long-throat is also gone, it must have been transferred to this side, the B-throat is also gone, it must be eliminated.
Okay, so after we have analyzed it, we will start to make the picture.
Let's open the front circle.
After opening it, when we are doing this kind of division, and this kind of division does not pass through any of the folds in the circle, we first draw the division.
There is another one, because it is an asymmetrical style.
When we are doing this picture, this picture is an asymmetrical style, and our circle is currently symmetrical.
So we need to right-click to unlock the link.
In this way, I can operate this asymmetrical style.
Look, we click on the left arrow.
Then the other color will no longer display the blue line.
Then click on the left arrow, and then set the internal line.
The distance of the internal line is the position of my division.
We can set it according to the style.
Let's assume it is 4 cm.
Okay, so after that, we will do the cutting line.
But the cutting line, because it is more complicated, there are more turns.
So now,
I will draw it separately.
I will draw it separately according to the traditional way.
So if all the folds are generally around the BP point,
you can not be at the BP point,
then the effect is not completely integrated.
It is not completely close.
And our style is an asymmetrical style.
And relatively speaking,
the fold is relatively not loose.
When the fold is formed, we do not have a simple straight BP point.
So our fold can actually be adjusted.
For example, like this position,
we can move this fold appropriately.
We select the fold,
select the fold,
one-third, ctrl-c, ctrl-v.
Then we drag it to this position.
This position,
you comprehensively consider the position of the fold.
And then the other half,
press the Shift key.
Then drag it to this position.
Okay, so after moving,
we can delete it if we can't use it at this time.
Okay,
delete this one too.
Okay.
Next,
I can adjust the length of the fold.
Adjust the length of the fold.
Make it shorter.
In fact,
it also increases the fold of the decorative lens.
The longer the fold pela,
the shorter the timespan.
Okay.
So then we can move the original
the left A position
to possibly move it to another place.
The next one is
the give us column small now.
we can actually divide it into a part
to this place, to the upper part of the sleeve
In this way, it forms a fold
and our style is a little closer
So how do we get it to the top?
We Ctrl C, Ctrl V
Then copy a line to refer to
Then we use the selection tool
Then go back to the other two-line tool
Then we double-click the center point
Then let it move over
Move to a BP point
Then we rotate
During the rotation, you can use a single-click to check the right-click angle
Of course, we can also measure its angle at the end
Of course, we can also measure its length at the end
After doing this, let's measure its length
It's 18.1
We can add points
Then its diameter is 18.1
This is the length of the sleeve
And then this hand, there must be a line along the edge of the hand
So let's add another point
Then pull it out
Then delete all the lines
Make it a straight line
Next, we can adjust its fold position
Then make it more uniform
Then we can adjust its fold position
We can see that the A and the A are closer to each other, and the A is more concentrated, so we can adjust it a little bit.
After adjusting, we can add another cutting line.
This is our analysis. After analyzing, we will cut the upper part of the shoulder.
After cutting, we will cut the throat.
After cutting the throat, it is actually the same as the original round shape.
After cutting, we will rotate it.
We still follow the principle that the front and center lines do not move.
Rotate and rotate, rotate and rotate, rotate and rotate.
Rotate and rotate, rotate and rotate.
The principle of the front and center line not moving.
Because it is a fold, there is no point of the throat.
We push the throat point to the cutting line.
After turning, the original line changes.
It doesn't matter.
The edge of the throat must be adjusted to equal length.
118.3, change the length.
118.3, 8,
Okay, there is no point of touch.
From the next step, press the border line of 2 throats, and enter the mouse button.
Press therier toCOCK , healthy, to scan the position.
At reference, in return point, we scan the small piece.
Travel the mouse.
Press the small piece.
Right click the mouse, open it.
Then we don't close the speaker and push it directly to the top
This speaker has also been transferred
Then after the transfer
We can delete it
Okay, let's transfer this part
Press the Shift key and click the edge of the two speakers
Press the right mouse button to rotate the speaker
Okay, the position of the new speaker is here
Then the point of the speaker
Rotate
Where are we rotating at this time
Let's see, the front center line is this place
This is the point of the front center line
So we need to rotate this way
We left-click and left-click
Then move the mouse
The top will open
Then push my mouse to the top
Don't let it become a speaker
Okay, our speaker has also been transferred
After transferring, we delete this
Of course, these are the auxiliary lines we made at the beginning
We can delete them
Click the left and right sides of the speaker
Press the right mouse button to rotate the speaker
The position of the new speaker
The point of the speaker is moved and left-clicked
Some students said
The top
The top of the neck changes
But the bottom is a straight line
Because there are too many folds on the top
There will definitely be a change
Then we move the point of the speaker
Push it to our segment line
Then we do the other side
The left and right side
We adjust this
Two speakers are equal
118.3
Adjust its length
Owen
It is
Unlock the keyboard
And turn it to the signal
Function
The туда
The bottom
Where the input noise of the speaker popularity
Then rotate and click on the small piece on the left
Okay, move the mouse and then let it merge the voice
Push the middle of the voice to the branch line
Okay, the next one
The next one, let's look at it
It's obvious that the two voices are not on the same side
At this time, we need to adjust the volume to 38.1
This one needs to be adjusted to 38.1
We choose the long one, click on the right mouse button to change the length
Then adjust the length to the end without moving the tip of the throat
38.1
Okay, I heard that this is not the original, let's go back and adjust it together
Okay, let's click on the Shift key and select the left and right mouse buttons
Okay
Click on the right mouse button to show the Rotate Voice
Then I set the voice position
Okay, then I set the voice position
Okay, then click on the voice position
At this time, we rotate
Click on the small piece and then this will open
Then push the voice point to the branch line
What if this place is not in the original order?
Let's adjust the original order
You can delete all the points
Then click on the circle to adjust the original order
Pay attention when adjusting, pay attention to this angle, try to make it 90 degrees
Because my back is 90 degrees
Okay, after adjusting
Then we look at this segment line, it has been stretched for a long time, it is very long
Then it will make the original order
At this time, we need to delete these more points
After deleting, then we use the editor tool
Then let it adjust the original order a little bit
Edit original order
Then put these unnecessary points, all of them are turned into free curve points
Delete the extra lines that are generated in the voice rotation process
Okay, let's go to the box
Before the box, delete the default box line that was generated when we did the voice rotation
Delete
We box the segment line
Box the key line
Box the side box, because it is an asymmetric model
So it can't come out at once
Because it is an asymmetric model, so it can't come out all of a sudden
Okay, then I'll pull out the 3D window at this time
This piece is because
The volume of voice rotation is relatively large
So we can turn it around appropriately
Okay, let me show you
Okay, it's basically close
But for example, we
This small piece, the small step piece is the short line of the shoulder segment line
This short line is stretched
So we didn't adjust it to 100% just now
So at this time, we adjust it to 100%
Unharden it